## HIKMATULLO MULLAJONOV

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

- +998 (94) 602-28-24
- **Q** Uzbekistan, Namangan
- https://www.hikmatdev.uz

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I have been working in the field of frontend programming since 2019. During this period, I have gained experience in creating and developing several web projects. I strive to constantly grow and develop as a developer, keeping up with modern technological innovations.

#### EDUCATION

#### 2017 - 2021

# TASHKENT UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

Computer engineering

#### ICT IT ACADEMY 2018 - 2019

Web programming

#### PDP IT ACADEMY 2019 - 2020

Web programming

#### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/Sass
- Bootstrap/Ant-design
- JavaScript
- ReactJS/Redux
- Typescript/ReactQuery
- Git/Github

#### LANGUAGES

Uzbek: Basic

English: Pre-Intermediate

• Russian: B1-B2

#### EXPERIENCE

### Webstar IT Academy

2022-2023

#### **Frontend Mentor**

- Webstar IT Training Center is a company that primarily deals with improving the level of web programming and computer literacy of school-age children.
- The following technologies are taught at Webstar: Html, Css, Bootstrap, Sass, JavaScript and React JS.
- This year I tried to expand my experience and convey my knowledge to my students as fully as possible.

#### **Webstar IT Academy**

2023 - PRESENT

### Frontend Mentor / Frontend Developer

Webstar Quiz Project

- This project is designed for students to take tests at the end
  of each module. For example, if html is completed, one
  exam test. The test results are saved, and the students'
  practice results can also be entered. In this way, the
  average test and practice score can be viewed
  automatically.
- In this project I created a user-friendly design and connected it to the backend. I also created an admin panel section to manage the site.

#### Webstar Gamification Project

- In this project, students complete step-by-step test assignments. For each completed test, they receive a fixed grade based on the section level. They can track their history and ratings in their profiles.
- In this project my task was to create a design that would be more interesting to readers and connected to the backend.
   In this project I used react/redux, for the design I chose antd.